{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
      "question": "Which ability from the &quot;Magic: The Gathering&quot; Scars of Mirrodin expansion involves having at least three artifacts in play?",
      "correct_answer": "Metalcraft",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Affinity",
        "Imprint",
        "Living Weapon"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
      "question": "Which board game was first released on February 6th, 1935?",
      "correct_answer": "Monopoly",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Risk",
        "Clue",
        "Candy Land"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
      "question": "Some of the &quot;Fallen Empires&quot; cards from &quot;Magic: The Gathering&quot; were misprinted on the backs of which other card game?",
      "correct_answer": "Wyvern",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Pokemon",
        "Dominion",
        "Yu-Gi-Oh"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
      "question": "The Dice Tower network of board game podcasts and videos is run by which individual?",
      "correct_answer": "Tom Vasel",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Jason LeVine",
        "Borth Sampson",
        "Uncle Pennybags"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
      "question": "The board game &quot;Monopoly&quot; is a variation of what board game?",
      "correct_answer": "The Landlord&#039;s Game",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Territorial Dispute",
        "Property Feud",
        "The Monopolist&#039;s Game"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
      "question": "In standard Monopoly, what&#039;s the rent if you land on Park Place with no houses?",
      "correct_answer": "$35",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "$30",
        "$50",
        "$45"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
      "question": "Which of these cards from &quot;Magic: The Gathering&quot; has a flavor text that begins with &quot;Oi oi oi&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Uthden Troll",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Lotleth Troll",
        "Albino Troll",
        "Harvester Troll"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
      "question": "Which character class in Dungeons and Dragons 5th edition gains it&#039;s powers from making a pact with a being of higher power?",
      "correct_answer": "Warlock",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Wizard",
        "Sorceror",
        "Cleric"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
      "question": "In Magic: The Gathering, which of the following was the first publicly released foil card?",
      "correct_answer": "Lightning Dragon",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Revenant",
        "Beast of Burden",
        "Dirtcowl Wurm"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
      "question": "What is the sum of all the tiles in a standard box of Scrabble?",
      "correct_answer": "187",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "207",
        "197",
        "177"
      ]
    }
  ]
}